<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1. VPC in AWS :: My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/1-vpc-in-aws/index.html</link>
    <description>In order to create EC2 instances, you need to have a VPC. It is isolated from other virtual networks in the AWS cloud. You can launch your AWS resources, such as EC2 instances, into your VPC. You can specify an IP address range for the VPC, add Subnets, associate Security Groups, and configure Route Tables. Finally, you can connect your VPC to the internet via Internet Gateway.&#xA;Content VPC Subnet Route Table Security Group Internet Gateway</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:10:14 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/1-vpc-in-aws/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1.1 VPC</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/1-vpc-in-aws/1-vpc/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:09:31 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/1-vpc-in-aws/1-vpc/index.html</guid>
      <description>Info All the AWS services in this lab will be initialized at the Asia Pacific (Singapore) region. Be sure to select this region before entering the lab.&#xA;Create VPC Go to VPC management console.&#xA;Click Your VPCs. Click Create VPC. At the Create VPC page, enter the following information:&#xA;Choose VPC only. Name tag: vpc-inference-1. IPv4 CIDR block: 10.10.0.0/28. Click Create VPC. After a VPC has been successfully created, you should edit some VPC configurations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.2 Subnet</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/1-vpc-in-aws/2-subnet/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:09:40 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/1-vpc-in-aws/2-subnet/index.html</guid>
      <description>Info Since there is currently no need for a database or other services, you will only create public subnet.&#xA;Create Public Subnet At the VPC management console:&#xA;Click Subnets. Click Create subnet. At the Create subnet page, enter the following information:&#xA;VPC: Choose the VPC with tag vpc-inference-1. Name tag: subnet-inference-1. Availability Zone: ap-southeast-1a. IPv4 subnet CIDR block: 10.0.0.0/28. Click Create subnet. After the subnet is created, the console will look like this.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.3 Route Table</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/1-vpc-in-aws/3-route-table/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:09:48 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/1-vpc-in-aws/3-route-table/index.html</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.4 Security Group</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/1-vpc-in-aws/4-security-group/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:09:58 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/1-vpc-in-aws/4-security-group/index.html</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.5 Internet Gateway</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/1-vpc-in-aws/5-internet-gateway/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:10:14 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/1-vpc-in-aws/5-internet-gateway/index.html</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>